http://marotta.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Marotta Controls, Inc.
Open Menu
MenuMARKETS CloseAEROSPACEMARINESPACEWEAPONSPRODUCTS CloseCONTROL SYSTEMSELECTROMECHANICAL ACTUATIONControl Actuation SystemsPNEUMATIC SYSTEMSAutomatic Fire Suppression SystemsIR Missile Seeker CoolingPneumatic Firing ValvesPneumatic Guillotine/Pneumatic CutterWeapon Ejection/ReleaseFLOW CONTROLSSOLENOID VALVESCoRe® Flow ControlsMiniature Solenoid ValvesPilot Operated/Direct ActingSubmersible ValvesPRESSURE CONTROLSCheck ValvesElectronic Pressure RegulatorsPressure Regulators/ReducersRelief ValvesSATELLITE PROPULSIONCold Gas MicrothrusterMiniature Solenoid ValvesMARINEAlignment FittingsAuto Stop/Excess Flow Check ValveChilled Water ValvesIn-Line Valve SystemsManifoldsSubsea – Deep Submergence ValvesQuick Closing ValvesPROPORTIONAL CONTROLSMulti-Function Proportional ControlPiezo Actuated ValvesPOWER ELECTRONICSELECTRONICSElectronic Motor ControllersPOWER1-STEP AC-DC Power ConversionPower Supply & ConversionSERVICES CloseDESIGN ENGINEERINGASSEMBLY & TESTMANUFACTURINGSUPPORT CloseAboutContactBusiness DevelopmentQualityRepair & Overhaul ServicesSupplier SupportTech Info / DownloadsNEWSCAREERS
MenuMARKETS CloseAEROSPACEMARINESPACEWEAPONSPRODUCTS CloseCONTROL SYSTEMSELECTROMECHANICAL ACTUATIONControl Actuation SystemsPNEUMATIC SYSTEMSAutomatic Fire Suppression SystemsIR Missile Seeker CoolingPneumatic Firing ValvesPneumatic Guillotine/Pneumatic CutterWeapon Ejection/ReleaseFLOW CONTROLSSOLENOID VALVESCoRe® Flow ControlsMiniature Solenoid ValvesPilot Operated/Direct ActingSubmersible ValvesPRESSURE CONTROLSCheck ValvesElectronic Pressure RegulatorsPressure Regulators/ReducersRelief ValvesSATELLITE PROPULSIONCold Gas MicrothrusterMiniature Solenoid ValvesMARINEAlignment FittingsAuto Stop/Excess Flow Check ValveChilled Water ValvesIn-Line Valve SystemsManifoldsSubsea – Deep Submergence ValvesQuick Closing ValvesPROPORTIONAL CONTROLSMulti-Function Proportional ControlPiezo Actuated ValvesPOWER ELECTRONICSELECTRONICSElectronic Motor ControllersPOWER1-STEP AC-DC Power ConversionPower Supply & ConversionSERVICES CloseDESIGN ENGINEERINGASSEMBLY & TESTMANUFACTURINGSUPPORT CloseAboutContactBusiness DevelopmentQualityRepair & Overhaul ServicesSupplier SupportTech Info / DownloadsNEWSCAREERS
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last Modified November 1, 2018
Purpose of our Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting marotta.com (the “Site”). This privacy policy and agreement (our “Privacy Policy”) governs and describes how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from and/or about you when you use the Site. We operate our Site pursuant to the statutes and regulations that apply to this Site (“Applicable Law”).
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. YOUR CONSENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY CREATES LEGAL OBLIGATIONS FOR YOU AND FOR US. IF YOU DO NOT CONSENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF OUR SITE.
Your Consent
By accessing and using our Site as a site visitor, you are acknowledging that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree to be legally bound by it. If you submit an inquiry to the Site, you will be asked to confirm that you have reviewed this Privacy Policy and that you agree to its terms. Confirmation constitutes your agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
The Site is owned and operated by Marotta Controls, Inc., a New Jersey corporation (“Marotta Controls,” “we,” “us,” and/or “our”), the entity that is responsible for the processing of the Personal Data collected on our Site, as described below. The Site has been created to provide information about our company and the “Services” to all users of the Site (the “Users”). This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy in regards to any information that is collected from Site visitors, including any personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) submitted.
Information Collected
When you interact with the Site or the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as described below.
Personal Data You Provide Through the Site: We collect Personal Data when you voluntarily provide such information, including when you use the “Submit an Inquiry” service. Personal Data may include contact information such as your name, email address, phone number and extension, and the purpose of your request. By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that such personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Marotta Controls.
Information We Collect When you Use the Site: When you interact with Marotta Controls through the Site or Services, we receive and store certain information about you. Such information may be collected passively using various technologies or other means described below.
Similar to most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. Marotta Controls may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Marotta Services affiliates, agents or service providers. The Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors’ ISPs, and how our users use and interact with the Services.
Cookie Policy
In operating the Site, we may also use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that we transmit to your browser when you access the Site. Our cookies help provide additionally functionality to the Site and help us analyze usage of the Site more accurately. In all cases where we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. Most web browsers include a “help” section in the toolbar that describes how to receive notification when receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site’s features.
The use of cookies by any of our affiliates or service providers is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.
Do Not Track & Google Analytics
Our Site does not respond to Do Not Track signals.
This Site uses Google Analytics. Google Analytics helps us to track viewing trends and analyze how visitors use the Site. This information helps us to improve the Site and overall user experience. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. None of the information collected is personally identifiable in nature without your express permission.
Use of Personal Data
Information collected by the Site will be used only to measure site activity, develop ideas for improving the Site, and respond to inquiries. We will never sell or rent information collected by the Site to any other company. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. We will endeavor to keep personal information accurate and up to date and to provide the opportunity to challenge the accuracy of the information. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Retention and Storage of Personal Data
We will not store information longer than required for the above-mentioned purposes.  Unless otherwise required by law, information collected during the submission of an inquiry will be deleted 24 months after the resolution that inquiry. Information collected during regular browsing of the site will be retained for a 36 month period.
The computer/servers in which we store identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
User Options
If your Personal Data changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete or request deletion by contacting our Marketing & Events Manager Katee Glass at either:
Phone: 973-334-7800
Email: support@marottacontrols.com
When you submit your information to the Site, we may send emails to you regarding your inquiry or to tell you about products we believe will be of interest to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to not receive an inquiry response or marketing emails by contacting our Customer Support at: support@marottacontrols.com.
Social Media
The Site also includes social media features such as the Facebook Like button, Twitter, and LinkedIn Share buttons. These features are interactive mini-programs and may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Facebook’s Privacy Policy is accessible here: https://www.facebook.com/policy.php
Twitter’s Privacy Policy is accessible here: https://twitter.com/en/privacy
LinkedIn’s Privacy Policy is accessible here: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
Not Intended For Children
Due to federal law (as reflected in the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), WE DO NOT ALLOW INDIVIDUALS WHO WE KNOW ARE UNDER 18 TO PARTICIPATE IN OUR SITE OR SERVICES. YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD TO USE OUR SITE AND SERVICES. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REQUEST PROOF OF AGE AT ANY POINT TO VERIFY THAT INDIVIDUALS UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE ARE NOT USING THE SITE OR SERVICES. IF WE BECOME AWARE THAT AN INDIVIDUAL UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE IS USING THE SITE OR SERVICES, WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO PROHIBIT AND BLOCK SUCH INDIVIDUAL FROM USING THE SITE OR SERVICES.
Links to Other Sites
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. This Site may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Marotta Controls (the “Third Party Sites”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from this Site do not imply that Marotta Controls endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those Third Party Sites directly for information on their privacy policies.
Relationship to Terms of Service
This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms of Service, and the provisions of our Terms of Service are incorporated herein. To the extent the Terms of Service conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of this Privacy Policy will control.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (if you have provided us with an email address) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact
Please feel free to contact our Marketing Manager, Katee Glass, if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, your privacy rights or the information practices of this Site, at the following:
Phone: 973-334-7800
Email: support@marottacontrols.com
programm wie excel kostenlos podcast herunterladen apple microsoften software tkkg computerspiel download kostenlos charts gratisen
© Marotta Controls, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Search
WordPress Download Manager - Best Download Management Plugin
Close
We use cookies to enhance your user experience. By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.OkLearn More
